(The 1st Rainbow Summer Retreat)
- Here. - It's smooth here.
Razor blades don't work on me now.
- Nine more people have to come. - Hello.
- My gosh. - Hey.
- Hello. - Why did you bring so much stuff?
I know, right?
- Hello. - I can tell this is bread.
It is. I wanted to share it with everyone on our way there.
I bet it's going to taste good.
(The 1st Rainbow Summer Retreat was announced last week.)
(Newsletter: The 2026 Rainbow Summer Retreat)
(It's been a while since I got anything printed on the pulp paper.)
(It brought old memories of my school retreats.)
(They will stay in a youth hostel in Suwon.)
(Happy to hear the news)
(Make sure to show up by 10am.)
- Have you been well? - Hey.
(Today is the day of the summer retreat.)
- There are four of us now. - Yes.
- My gosh. - Hello.
- You're here. - Nice to see you, everyone.
(Hello.)
He said hello five times.
- It was so awkward then. Right? - Nice to meet you.
- I'm Seo Bum June. - It was so awkward.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
- I'm Seo Bum June. - You guys have never met before?
- It's our first time meeting. - Yes.
- They've never met before. - I see.
Do you know who these two guys are?
- They're actors, right? - Yes.
- "Actors." - And you are...
- What's his name? - You are Bae Na Ra.
- You're Seo Bum June. - My gosh.
- I was nervous. - Name a project they're famous for.
A project they're famous for? Well,
- you were in that thing. - What?
You were in that impressive action scene.
- An impressive action scene. - What's the title?
- The title? - It's "Impressive Action Scene?"
"Weak Hero."
(He remembers it.)
You were in "Weak Hero."
And don't you love bread?
- You love bread. - Yes. And my famous project?
Your famous project is I Live Alone.
(The project he's famous for is I Live Alone?)
- I'm sorry, Bum June. - I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
- You need to work harder. - I'll work harder.
(The actor with 2 Rookie Awards in 2024 is disappointed.)
- I'll make sure to watch it. - Yes.
- Hello. - It's Dae Ho.
- Hello. - Hi.
(The members are arriving one at a time.)
- Hello. - Gosh.
It's Park Gyeong Hye.
- There are a lot of people. - It's so crowded.
There are so many people.
The fashionista is here.
Right.
Joy.
(Joy and MINHO are the last ones to arrive.)
MINHO.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hey. This is crazy. - We were a big group.
- It's so crowded. - He's so handsome.
Hello. Yes. Nice to meet you.
That was random.
- What's going on? - There's more?
- No way. - No way.
- No way. - For real?
Stop that.
(Loving it)
He was so cool!
- That was so hip, right? - It was so cool.
It was really cool.
It's him!
(Driver Ku, the designated driver of the retreat)
(Amazed)
(Cheering wholeheartedly)
Make some noise!
- Yes! - Let's go!
Hey, get in!
"Hey, get in."
Gosh, for real?
This is embarrassing.
- That's so cool. - This is amazing.
Sir!
(You just trust me.)
- That's cool. - It's so funny.
Come on in. Wait. Let me park it.
- Give me a second. - Academy bus drivers...
looked just like him back in my day.
- He also wore gloves. - Yes, the gloves.
- He was very detailed. - Yes.
All right. Don't act cheeky now.
- Drive safely. - It's not easy to drive a van.
I've tried it once.
- Do you need help? - Gosh, no. It's heavy.
- No. - Gosh.
(Grabbing)
- My gosh. Oh, no. - No. It's light.
Let me help you.
- Seon Min, that was cool. - That was Seon Min.
(What was that? That was pretty cool.)
Well, I think it's basic etiquette.
"Etiquette?"
(Laughing)
- Your bags... - We can put them in here, right?
Carefully load them in the trunk one at a time.
I know, right? Bum June.
All right. Get in.
- I should sit here. - I wasn't there.
- You were getting ready for it. - I was hosting my radio show.
I'll make sure you all get in safely.
(I'll see everyone get in.)
- You're like a professional driver. - Gosh.
Don't you worry about it.
I have the Class One license to drive large vehicles.
- Really? - Yes.
- You do? - Yes.
- Are you a good driver? - Come on, Hyun Moo.
My nickname is Mad Max.
- Mad Max? - Yes.
It must be dangerous then.
(What a nickname.)
Seat belts. Are you all settled in?
- Yes. - Yes.
- We're not leaving anyone behind. - Okay.
I'll close the door for you.
(I'll close the door for you.)
Let's go.
I like this.
- Gosh, thank you. - Really?
I brought rice cakes. Have some rice cakes.
- She bought rice cakes. - Oh, my.
- She bought rice cakes. - Thank you!
- My gosh. - They were really good.
- My gosh. Thank you. - Here.
I also bought bread on my way here.
- My gosh. - Pass it up.
- They're chosen by Bum June. - Thank you, Bum June.
- They're chosen by Bum June. - That's amazing.
This is a palate cleanser.
(Seon Min also shares Shinbi peaches.)
Shinbi peaches!
They were good, right?
My father runs a small peach farm.
- Really? - Yes.
- They were so good. - But I'm sorry.
The season is over. I can get more next year.
I already bought 5kg of those peaches.
- Really? - Do you sell fruit?
(What on earth?)
- This is sulbbang. - It's sulbbang?
- I washed everything. Have one. - We don't need to eat breakfast.
Seeing how Bum June bought this, this must be the best tart now.
- Right. - I should've skipped my radio show.
(Joking)
- I should've done that. - Because of the bread?
Because of the bread, rice cakes, and fruit?
Please drive safely.
My gosh, don't worry. My nickname is Mad Max.
- Don't worry. - Great.
- Let's go. - My gosh.
(They finally set out on their summer retreat.)
(Back in the day, the bus rides to the retreat were full of fun.)
That was the old days.
That was the school retreat.
Right. Pillow fights are fun.
Right, pillow fights.
(It was even more joyful with friends.)
It's "Pebble Love" by Seo Min Ho.
That's not the title.
"Pebble Love?" My gosh. I haven't heard that in a while.
I loved the playlist.
(Romance is long gone, and only trot songs fill the air.)
I bet CODE KUNST is getting inspired a lot today.
(I bet CODE KUNST is getting inspired a lot today.)
I bet he can write new songs right away.
- Do you still exercise these days? - These days?
- You run, right? - I do.
Running is the easiest for me.
It's the safest, right?
(Turning back)
Do you still run a lot?
- You run every day, right? - Yes. I run a lot.
- I watched a lot of your clips. - I see.
I saw you exercise in those clips.
It was awkward, so I wanted to find some common ground.
(Chuckling)
Why don't we go for a run together?
I can run at your pace.
Don't worry about that.
(Approaching again)
- Kian84. - Yes?
- I'm used to running by myself. - Okay.
Sometimes, running gets boring.
(What should I do?)
You should run with MINHO. It gets better then.
- It reminded me of college days. - Okay.
At orientation trips, some kids would start conversations...
- Right. - to get to know each other.
- Exactly. - He kept talking to everyone.
I'll think about what kind of run we can do together.
- That sounds good. - So...
This was my first time today.
- Things are awkward in the back. - My gosh.
A talent show?
(Feeling awkward)
Do you typically stay quiet when you get in the car?
I usually go to sleep because I get carsick.
- Same here. - What about you?
- I don't get shy around new people. - Okay.
- But at first... - Are you just being careful?
I might come across as rude. So I'm just being careful now.
I don't know what to say now.
I like this subtle awkwardness.
- I like that too. - Me too.
I rarely have occasions these days where I can feel that.
(Treat me right when you have me)
(Clueless of what's going on in the back,)
(the guys in the front are just having fun.)
Are you going to sing for the talent show?
- What? - Will you sing?
- Sing? Today? - For the talent show.
It's a secret.
- You should drop the honorifics. - Really?
Please drop the honorifics with me too.
Really?
That's when you guys dropped the honorifics.
Yes. They said we should drop the honorifics.
How old is everyone? How old is Bum June?
- They're around the same age. - Yes, we're around the same age.
We're 1 or 2 years apart.
I have a hard time doing that. But let me try.
(They are bonding as they drop the honorifics.)
It's already funny.
(The members are getting close to Suwon.)
- It's giving youth hostel vibes. - We're in the suburbs.
(A van drives along on a quiet road.)
- Everyone, here's our youth hostel. - My gosh.
(At last!)
Gosh, a youth hostel.
- No way. - They were the bomb back then.
This place is really nice.
- It's nice. - There's a podium too.
Of course, there is.
- No way. - My gosh.
How nostalgic.
It's our first summer retreat.
(They arrive at the lush, green retreat venue.)
Gosh, this place looks great.
- No way. - My gosh.
I love it.
This is utopia.
- This is a nice place. - Which way?
- The summer retreat. - On the left.
- Thank you! - Thank you.
Let's go.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Thank you for driving, Driver Ku.)
My gosh.
(They quickly get out of the van with excitement.)
It felt like I was a kid again.
- Didn't it make you giddy? - Super giddy.
- Let's go. - This place looks great, right?
- It looks great. - They kept the place nice.
- I love it. - This place looks amazing.
You know what? It feels like I'm on a school retreat.
- Totally. - A school retreat.
Kids used to wear flip-flops...
- to school retreats. - Definitely.
This is nice.
Kids with big backpacks used to have beer in them.
- They also hid it under the shirts. - Back in the day, kids did that...
behind the teachers.
(Just like the old days...)
- How old is this clip? - Seriously. What year is that from?
- I bet it was from 1989. - Seriously.
I can't share rooms with Hyun Moo. He snores.
You snore too.
- I can't be his roommate. - I'll snore right into your ear.
I wonder what we're doing today on the field.
I haven't been to a youth hostel in a while.
- He looks excited. - We should play soccer.
Let's find four-leaf clovers.
- Four-leaf clovers? - Has anyone found them?
- This is nice. - Oh, how nice.
It's been a while since I stepped on grass.
- Exactly. - Right.
They tell us not to step on it.
It's not allowed anywhere now.
I caught a long-headed grasshopper.
- A long-headed grasshopper? - A long-headed grasshopper?
- I caught it instantly. - No way.
-They're rare these days. - He loves bugs, indeed.
This one is a baby.
No. Don't show it to me.
- Not me. - Surprisingly, he hates bugs.
- Right, he hates them. - Yes.
You didn't catch bugs as a kid?
- I used to do that a lot as a kid. - Don't eat that.
- Don't eat it, Seon Min. - This is a great protein source.
(Joking)
- Don't eat that, Seon Min. - Gosh.
President Jun.
- All right. - Okay.
- What's that? - It looks a bit weird.
- Are you not wearing pants? - He looks cute.
- All right. Today is... - I look weird.
- What a spot for the banner. - That looks weird.
There wasn't a lectern.
I'm going to announce the schedule for our summer retreat.
First of all, thank you for coming all the way to Suwon.
(He starts off by welcoming them.)
Thank you.
Hyun Moo prepared everything for the retreat.
I put together the program for the retreat.
There were many options I could have chosen from.
But I chose this youth hostel for a reason.
We live alone. But we're here to learn...
- Right. We... - the value of working together.
- We never had a chance to do this. - The overall theme...
of our program is working together.
- Okay. - That's our theme.
- So... - We're a team.
- We're a team. - Okay.
Remember what I told you to bring?
- Yes. - Yes.
What did I tell you to bring?
- Food! - Ingredients for bibimbap!
- Ingredients for bibimbap. - Yes.
- Did you all bring them? - I really wanted to do this.
Okay. I'm going to start by checking your backpacks first.
- You'll do it here? - Right here?
- I had to check their bags. Yes. - You checked their bags?
And we're going to eat right after that.
(Cheering)
(Is that a scream of joy?)
He was super happy.
- He was hungry. - I was hungry.
Because he had to drive.
- We'll eat right away. - Since this is the summer retreat,
I must check...
- Students? - if the students brought liquor.
I'll check if you brought an ingredient too.
Great.
Dae Ho, you brought food. Right?
- What? I did. - You brought food, right?
Yes. It's edible.
I thought we agreed not to invite him.
- We have to bring... - An ingredient for random bibimbap.
- This is important. - What's this?
We'll have random bibimbap for lunch.
Don't discuss it. Just bring an ingredient you want.
- Sir. - Yes?
Will Kim Dae Ho and Kian84 also bring an ingredient?
(Why would you ask that?)
(On the last Innocent Moo-Ku Fall Field Day)
It tastes weird, right?
It tastes a bit weird.
It's bibimbap.
(Dae Ho's bibimbap from the abyss)
- Gosh. - Seriously.
- Dae Ho, don't play with food. - Kian84 should go last.
I'm going to do the bag check now.
It's been a long time since I got a bag check.
- Here? - Yes.
I'm so curious.
I brought a great ingredient.
I'm sure everyone will compliment me for my ingredient.
- Really? - Mine will be crazy.
- I can't wait for Sung Hwan's. - Let's begin.
- Let's start with Ji Hyeon. - Let me go first.
- Look at his bag. - Actually, he's a great cook.
- Of course. - I went with a classic ingredient.
- Classic is the best. - That's the best.
- What if we overlap? - Classic ingredients.
- Look. He's got a stick. - When we did the Fun Run,
- Gosh. - we got to taste his food.
- What's that? - It's young radish kimchi.
- I loved it. - Seriously.
- The perfect summer ingredient! - Yes.
You were off to a great start.
- That's the best summer food. - Great.
This is great.
- We needed this. - It's important.
- It smelled great. - Yes.
- The kimchi from Jeolla Province. - It's perfectly fermented.
It's perfectly fermented.
It smells so good.
- This is great. You pass. - It's the real deal.
- Thank you. - It's great.
You brought a great ingredient. But I still need to conduct...
- a bag check. - Okay.
- I must check if you have liquor. - Gosh, I didn't.
- Let me check your bag. - He's got a cane.
- A cane. - This.
- Well, young radish kimchi... - I brought clothes and underwear.
Underwear.
- You have gray underwear. - And shoes.
- You pass. - This...
"You pass?"
- Underwear? - What's going on?
(Conducting a thorough bag check)
- I wanted to see what he had. - No, not that.
- That's too much. - What is it?
- Why not? What's in it? - No. That's...
That's... No.
- What is it? - Let me see.
- For the talent show? - Gosh.
- For the talent show. - The talent show.
Everyone tried to hide their items for the talent show.
- Right. - I see.
We'll check everything but the items for the talent show.
- Okay. Young radish kimchi! - Okay.
(Ji Hyeon easily passes the bag check.)
That looks good.
- Gosh, young radish kimchi. - He brought a great ingredient.
- I love young radish kimchi. - Next up is...
After young radish kimchi... Should I go next?
- Let's do it. - Here's why.
Mine goes well with young radish kimchi.
- Dried laver flakes? - Let's check.
- My gosh. - Come on. Hurry.
That's great.
He brought two containers.
- They're side dish containers. - You had to bring only one.
- What is it? - His ingredient was great too.
- I cut it. - Is it doenjang?
- What is it? - Fried tofu?
- Is it doenjang? - I'm so curious.
- Is that jangjorim? - It's ham.
- Ham. Yes. - Gosh.
- I knew it. - Seriously. You know what?
- That's crazy. - Where did you get that?
(Approving)
- Great. - Shin Young.
He brought SPAM that was as big as a loaf of bread.
- You can buy that. - I've never seen that before.
- I've never seen that before. - You can eat that with a spoon.
- That's crazy. - It was a block.
- I knew it. - I brought a block of SPAM.
I also air-fried it.
- We can mash it. - Of course, it should be fried.
- Yes. - This is crazy.
- Smell it. - The ingredients...
- That looks good. - He also fried it.
- That's a great combo. - Nice.
- We've got good momentum now. - Great.
- I brought... - My mom...
- a trendy ingredient on Instagram. - Look at his pouch.
It's a trendy ingredient.
- A trendy ingredient. - I don't know what it is.
- The pouch is trendy? - No way.
- What is it? I don't know. - It can't be bread, right?
- No way. - Is it beef?
I made it myself.
- What is it? - My goodness.
- My goodness. - You can cook Korean food too?
Have you heard about beef gochujang with garlic scapes?
It was super good.
- No way. - No way.
You can have an entire meal...
- with just that. - I hope it's good.
- You brought the best ingredient. - Bum June. Seriously.
Bum June is super thorough.
He even measured his ingredient...
- and brought the perfect amount. - Yes.
- He measured it? - Yes.
He brought enough for everyone?
No way.
This looks so neat.
- I brought 800g. - He brought 800g.
- He can cook Korean food well too. - Hey, he double-wrapped it.
- He can cook Korean food well too. - You made this yourself?
Bibimbap with just these three ingredients would be tasty.
- So far... - It's perfect.
- So far... - It's perfect so far.
Can't we just add these three?
Who's next?
You seem anxious.
(Flinching)
Wait.
- That's an anxious gaze. Why? - You didn't bring any?
- You didn't bring anything? - Gosh.
I forgot it at the MBC building.
- My gosh. - It's on the way now.
- My gosh. - Oh, no.
- You left it there? - It will arrive before we mix them.
- I made sure of that. - We're going to mix them now.
It will come in ten minutes. Please.
You must've been so flustered. When did you realize it?
I realized it when we began the bag checks.
I pulled it out of my bag for a second...
because of the smell. And I forgot it there.
You must've been so anxious...
- when we opened our ingredients. - He must've been so nervous.
(His face turned pale as they continued.)
I was so anxious.
It will come in ten minutes. Please give me some time.
- Do the push-up position. - Okay.
(That kind of mindset won't do for our retreat.)
Oh, no.
- Gosh. - That hurts.
It broke after the first use?
It broke.
I guess he farted when Hyun Moo hit him.
Bring him a new one.
Mine isn't fancy like that.
- Canned tuna, right? - What is it?
- What is it? I see clothes. - What's that?
- I'm seeing towels. - Right.
- Right here. - It already doesn't look tasty.
Gosh. I bet he brought canned tuna.
- No. - Tuna?
- Is it jangjorim? - Is it...
(You still think it's not good?)
- Gosh. - That's the most important one.
- Sesame oil. - Hey.
- The most important ingredient. - What a relief.
- It's a must-have ingredient. - It was my first food compliment.
- Gosh, nice. - It was the most important one.
- It was the best. - It was the most important one.
- Nice. - What a relief.
- Is it from a mill? - We're saved.
- Here. - Amazing, right?
- We're good. - We're good now.
It'd taste good with just these four ingredients.
- Totally. - First of all...
We're off to an amazing start.
- We've got everything we need. - Yes.
- I brought beef gochujang. - Nice.
(I brought beef gochujang.)
- We brought similar ingredients. - It's okay.
- Right. But we need more. - Mine has garlic scapes.
- Great. - We can add mine.
I felt so bad.
But it was different from the one with garlic scapes.
- It was the original version. - Of course.
Sir, I have high blood pressure. If I eat this bibimbap,
it might spike to 200.
- We'll add a lot of rice. - We will, right?
Great.
- That's... - It's for the bibimbap.
It's young radish kimchi!
(She brought the same ingredient as Ji Hyeon.)
- Is it from the store? - It's from Jun Myun.
- Park Jun Myun? - Yes.
- It smells amazing. - Gosh.
Park Jun Myun's kimchi is great.
She's an amazing cook.
- It's good. - She sends me kimchi every season.
She always sends me kimchi when I'm about to run out of it.
Okay. Joy, show us yours now.
My ingredient didn't overlap at all.
Mine is pretty good.
- But I might need to get punished. - I'm so curious about hers.
- Why? - What is it? She brought one.
It's in the insulated bag.
I brought flowers.
- What? - Flowers?
- Edible flowers. - Flowers?
(How beautiful...)
We already had a lot of salty ingredients.
- Right. - It was fine.
I bet it will look pretty.
We need to take pictures.
We can add flowers!
(Let's eat pretty bibimbap with flowers.)
- She gave it a lot of thought. - What a great idea.
- Not to overlap. - She brought unique ingredients.
Her flowers definitely improved how our bibimbap looked.
- Yes. - Right.
I'll go next.
I'm so curious about yours.
- I... - He wouldn't tell us.
- Luckily, we didn't overlap. - Sesame oil is great.
You guys need dried laver flakes.
- Don't take out energy gel. - No.
- Energy gel. - I bet he brought chicken breast.
I really wanted this...
- in the bibimbap. - What is it?
- So I made it myself this morning. - It's protein for sure.
- You made this? - Yes.
- Fried eggs? - Fried eggs.
(Fried eggs)
(Cheering)
- Common ingredients are the best. - We're good.
- Great. - We definitely need that.
- We didn't have eggs. - We've got everything now.
- We needed eggs. - Totally.
- He was so thoughtful. - He made a lot too.
- Imagine bibimbap without them. - Right.
- I fried 20 eggs. - Gosh, 20 eggs?
- Nice. - I knew no one would bring eggs.
- It's hard to fry 20 at home. - We need protein.
- It took 30 minutes this morning. - Exactly.
- You were super thoughtful. - Right? Gosh, what a relief.
I knew no one would bring them.
The most common ingredient, but the most necessary one.
- Nice, MINHO. - My gosh.
We almost had bibimbap without eggs.
- Right. This is... - Nicely done.
Gosh, he brought the perfect ingredient.
- Right. - You guys needed eggs.
- All right. Kian84 and Dae Ho. - I knew no one would bring them.
- For some reason... - I...
For some reason, I kept feeling self-conscious about my food.
- All right. - Let's start with Kian84.
It looks like...
so far, we have ingredients we can easily mix with rice.
- Yes. - We don't have side dishes.
- He's gotten chatty. - Can you bring side dishes?
And I didn't overlap with anyone.
- I didn't overlap. - Really? That's good.
It's...
- What is it? - I bet it's young radish kimchi.
(Their eyes are glued to Kian84's hands.)
And I didn't overlap with anyone.
Really? That's good.
- It's... - Stir-fried anchovies?
- What is it? - I bet it's young radish kimchi.
It's cabbage kimchi!
(No, it's not! It's cabbage kimchi!)
- Really? - It's kimchi.
- Gosh. - That looks so good.
(Salivating)
- Great. - Dae Ho.
It would be crazy if you took out beef.
- That would be amazing. - No. He's...
Come on.
- Here it goes. - My gosh.
- What is it? - No.
(Anxious)
- Look at the way he's carrying it. - Let me explain.
He made no effort.
It's not that I made no effort. Let me explain.
- We're sharing everything. - Yes.
I didn't bring any food I would eat on my own.
I made an effort.
- It's not salted oyster, right? - Salted oyster?
No way. Did you also bring kimchi?
I didn't put the food in a resealable bag.
You scared me.
- You just brought an opaque bag. - They don't like it.
Actually, I prepared for this since yesterday.
I had a feeling you'd bring salty ingredients.
So I didn't season it.
- Hey, that sounds weird! - I have a bad feeling about this.
- Did he bring seasoned vegetables? - I guess he cooked.
- Well, it's something like that. - Come on.
- I brought... - What's that?
minced beef.
- What? - What?
- I added shishito peppers. - We're good!
(Touched)
- Gosh, Dae Ho! - Goodness.
- Nice. - That's the best one.
- Hey. Dae Ho. - That's the best ingredient.
- He was surprisingly thoughtful. - I didn't season it.
(Dae Ho finally learned how to use containers.)
I can smell it.
- It smells great. - Dae Ho, you...
I can smell the shishito peppers.
- We're all going to share it. - No way.
- You know what? - What a surprise.
- I can smell it. - It smells so good.
- He was criticized quite harshly. - Look at that.
Right. The criticism was quite harsh last time.
You're the best, Dae Ho.
Did you make it yourself?
I made it last night.
The cabbage kimchi feels neglected.
Their reaction for my ingredient was the shortest.
We're used to seeing that in the cafeteria.
(Feeling sorry)
- President Jun is the last one. - Hyun Moo.
- Let me open yours. - No one brought vegetables.
- No one brought vegetables. - I brought this for the flavors.
- For the flavors? - I brought it for the flavors.
- Canned tuna? - What's this?
Take it out.
- This is... - What's that?
- What is it? - Isn't that liquor?
- What is that? - We can't add that.
- Is it yakgwa? - It's a Mexican sauce.
- It's the Mexican taco sauce. - What's that?
(Mexican taco sauce)
- Taco! - What's that?
You bought this in Mexico when you were there.
That looks good, though.
- Come on. - I brought a variety pack.
- It's a fusion dish. - Come on.
This is really good.
Sung Hwan didn't like that.
- Look at him. - He doesn't look happy.
See? Sung Hwan and I...
- are on the same page. - You both like Korean food.
- Local people there eat this a lot. - Does it go well with bibimbap?
- It does. - I'm sure.
- Gosh, no. You honestly think so? - They will go well together.
- It tastes amazing with SPAM. - Really?
(It tastes amazing especially with SPAM.)
(Really?)
He's easily influenced.
- He just criticized the sauce. - Right.
- It's made with local green chilis. - The edible flowers...
So this one is...
I had a feeling...
- you'd bring common ingredients. - What's that?
- What's that? - Spicy Italian anchovies.
- Anchovies. - That was interesting.
- Anchovies. - That's...
(Anchovies from abroad?)
All right. It's time for our meal now!
- Yes! - Yes!
Sung Hwan and I will go and get rice.
- Yes. - The cafeteria made rice for us.
- We can leave our stuff here. - Yes.
- Leave your bags and rest up. - Gosh, sesame oil.
Bum June. One, two.
One, two, three.
(Na Ra is taking pictures of the members.)
- I'm glad you brought that. - Oh, that's nice.
You guys were having fun.
- You took pictures of them. - Gosh, the pictures were great.
- Not bad, right? - Yes. Eggs...
I had a feeling no one would bring them.
Fried eggs are the best.
Fried eggs.
I just flipped them with the spatula.
How many eggs did you cook in the pan?
- Three. I had a big pan. - Three?
(Rushing)
I was so anxious.
Where are you going?
My food is here. I'll go and get it.
I bet they'll bring a lot of rice since Sung Hwan went with him.
- They're coming. - Here they come.
Look at that. That's a whole bucket.
- My gosh. - Is this "The Walking Dead?"
Seriously.
- It's huge. - Gosh.
Everyone, grab one.
- There are 12 of us. - It's heavy.
- How many... - Look at the rice.
Where... My gosh.
- Good job. - Look at the rice.
Oh, my.
Should we add them now?
We can add all of my SPAM.
- Yes. Let's add the whole thing. - Yes.
- It's the mild version. - It's not salty?
(Adding the block of SPAM into the bowl first)
That must be salty enough.
It will be salty enough with that.
- You need to mash it. - It's...
- Wear gloves and use your hands. - I see.
Gloves.
- Bum June is so thoughtful. - It's salty enough.
- Should we add gochujang next? - Yes.
Does the order matter?
- No. - Mine...
- Let's add everything in one go. - Let's add everything now.
Let's add everything to the middle, but not too much.
(They huddle up...)
(and add beef with shishito peppers.)
The shishito peppers look great.
Gosh, did you get your food?
- Did you get your food? - I got it.
Vegetables!
Stir-fried dried radish greens in doenjang.
- It smells like the countryside. - It's homemade.
The doenjang from the countryside.
Seon Min, add everything.
Seon Min's ingredient has a taste of the countryside.
- Should I pour everything out? - Yes.
- Here. - It's the taste of the countryside.
That looks great.
- Gosh, this is crazy. - Next...
That looks good.
We have so much food.
- Hold on. - Wait.
- Should I add this? - We have so much food.
(Quietly trying to dump cabbage kimchi)
You sneakily tried to dump the kimchi.
(Sensing danger)
- Hold on. - You guys liked this earlier.
- Wait. - Step back.
- That's so precious. - Not yet.
- Let's add that later. - The order didn't matter.
(Well, there's nothing I can do.)
Gyeong Hye, let's add your young radish kimchi.
- My young radish kimchi? - Your young radish kimchi.
- Should I add everything? - I think we can add everything.
- Everything including the juice. - First of all, let's add this.
- Everything. - Without the juice?
- It's okay. Add everything. - The juice...
Should I add the kimchi juice?
- Add it. - No. We can add that later.
- Not the juice. It's too salty. - Could you speak one at a time?
- No. We can add that later. - Could you speak one at a time?
Some are going, "Add the sauce." Others are going, "Leave it out."
- That's right. - It'll be too salty.
- Let's add some more. - Come on.
No. Leave the sauce out for now.
We can sprinkle it on the top later.
Good thinking.
- Next. - Here.
- Shall I add these? - Eggs.
- Eggs. - Add the eggs.
- Eggs are a must. - Eggs.
- Nice. I'm glad you brought them. - Add the eggs.
- Let's add the eggs. - Add all of them.
Add all of them.
- Okay. - Adding a lot makes it tasty.
(They add all of the fried eggs.)
- I'll add half of it. - Okay.
It looks tasty.
- Next. - What's next?
(Glancing over)
There is beef gochujang too.
- We added some gochujang. - Guys.
Until when will you keep it Korean cuisine?
- No! - Oh, my!
- No! - You can't add them!
- You can't add anchovies! - They're so tasty.
Eat them by yourself.
- Release them in the water. - That's right.
- It's funky. - Oh, my.
- It's funky. - Is it Italian salted seafood?
- It's different. - Let me take a sniff.
Salted seafood.
- I see. - It's a bit stinky.
- It smells tasty. - I don't think we can add them.
Joy says yes to most things.
- Hyun Moo, didn't they go bad? - No, they didn't.
Release them in the water.
How many anchovies will you add?
Oh, my.
(He suddenly adds one.)
I see that it went in.
(Oh, my gosh)
- I released it. - He is releasing fish.
Here is the sauce.
- No! - Hey!
(They become shocked and stop him.)
Okay.
- Everyone hated the idea. - I thought fish would jump out.
These kids don't know how to eat.
- Can't we add this? - I think we're set.
- All right. - Hey.
Let's add Kian84's kimchi now.
- Let's add Kian84's kimchi now. - Kimchi is a must.
(Kian84, wait.)
(A moment ago, they stopped him from adding his ingredient.)
(He waited for his chance with kimchi in his hand.)
He stood there the whole time.
My kimchi needs to go in.
(My kimchi needs to go in, so leave out the sauce!)
All right.
- He was anxious. - Let's add Kian84's kimchi now.
- People finally accepted it. - That's right.
Look at the color.
We're getting the right color now.
I even cut this kimchi into bite-sized pieces!
(I even cut this kimchi into bite-sized pieces!)
- Kian84, it improved the color. - The color?
- It improved the color. - I see. The color is popping.
We're getting the right color now.
It looks legit.
(The color looks more appetizing.)
Look at the color.
- Someone should try it. - I'll try it.
(It's time to try it.)
We can season it more, right?
- Did we add too many ingredients? - You know,
- all the flavors got mixed up. - Okay.
We should add an ingredient with strong flavors.
- It needs more anchovies. - No!
It doesn't need more anchovies.
Of course not.
- Let's add some sesame oil. - That's a great idea.
- Sesame oil is a must. - Add sesame oil.
- Add sesame oil. - Why didn't you add it sooner?
Shall I add more anchovies?
(Hung up on the idea)
No, Hyun Moo.
We don't need them! We told you 800 times!
Why do you keep bringing up anchovies?
(He explodes in the end.)
It was my first time seeing Sung Hwan that angry.
- I know. - He was seriously angry.
I thought he was Pavarotti.
(Ku Pavarotti is sensitive when it comes to food.)
The flavors of anchovies are too strong.
Too much is as bad as too little.
- I see. - We added all the gochujang.
I can't handle spicy food.
- I find it tasty. - I find it tasty too.
We're nearly done.
It was nice. It was seasoned perfectly.
Let's add the flowers now.
It's a heart.
Bum June is detailed.
Oh, my.
(Joy's flowers get sprinkled on the top.)
- It looks artistic. - It's visually appealing.
- It's pretty. - How pretty!
- It's visually appealing. - It's pretty.
- It's tasty. - Is it tasty?
Which one do you want?
- That's enough for me. - Okay.
(He begins to scoop out food.)
Were you a military cook?
- He is good at scooping. - Seon Min is good at scooping.
- He is good at scooping. - There are chili peppers.
- Seriously. - Thank you for the food.
- Enjoy the food. - Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for the food. - Enjoy the food.
- Thank you for the food. - My goodness.
It's nice to gather around and eat.
- Bibimbap should be eaten that way. - It's tasty.
Dae Ho.
- The shishito peppers... - The shishito peppers are good.
- Are they crunchy? - They add crunchiness to the dish.
I didn't overcook them.
All the ingredients go well together.
- I know. It's so tasty. - I missed the tasty food.
It's so delicious.
You know,
you can see Kian84's kimchi if you look very closely.
It used to be red,
but it's white now. I can still taste the flavors.
I think your kimchi deepened the colors of the dish.
- The colors? - Yes, the colors.
(Your kimchi deepened the colors of the dish!)
MINHO, you look after me whenever we're in a group setting.
(Shy)
Kian84, I always look after you.
Recently...
I always cry on the inside even though I don't say anything.
Thank you.
He is good at complimenting people.
It put me in a good mood.
Stop being so proud...
and ask me for more anchovies if you want them.
- That's how you eat it. - With fish?
(Getting up)
What?
Hyun Moo, please give me one anchovy.
Gosh, this Fun Run member knows how to eat.
This bowl has two.
Really?
- Here are two. - Anchovy addicts...
began to show up.
It's tasty. It isn't spicy or fishy.
I ate about eight anchovies.
- They're so salty. - You ate more than Italians.
- They were salty but tasty. - So they were tasty.
Hyun Moo, they're so tasty.
- I'll drink 5l of water later. - It's a unique ingredient.
- They're so tasty. - Look at him.
He became hooked on anchovies.
Later on,
- everyone wanted them. - They're good.
How does the dish taste when you add them?
Is the taste similar to that of salted oysters?
It's salted seafood...
- that's less spunky. - That's right.
- It isn't so fermented. - They're stored in olive oil,
so they aren't very fishy.
They aren't very fishy. I don't like such fishy food.
There is only a bit of fishiness.
- I see. - Why did you smack your lips?
I don't know. It really hurts my pride.
I didn't know that you saw it.
- It hurts my pride. - She gulped.
(It hurts my pride that I don't know the taste.)
I doubt any restaurants serve bibimbap this hearty.
Of course.
Dae Ho's contribution made it more like bibimbap.
I know.
I'm jealous that you guys had such a nice meal.
Dae Ho, why are you eating with your hand?
I'm mixing the ingredients as I eat.
(He is enjoying mixing the ingredients with his hand.)
(Oh, my)
(Scraping)
- It's so tasty. - This is incredible.
- It's very delicious. - He isn't using a spoon.
Everyone is eating differently.
Seon Min, you ate a lot.
It's so tasty.
It's perfectly normal to eat three bowls.
You're on your third bowl. Sung Hwan is eating the most.
(Stuffing his face)
Really?
(The food is accompanied by cool beverages.)
(They enjoy the beverages as they eat bibimbap.)
It has zero calories.
- It has zero calories. - Yes.
It contains many good ingredients.
You can drink it without feeling bad.
It's so tasty.
(Downing it)
(My goodness)
It goes really well with food.
(Satisfied)
- Seriously. It's nice. - There you go.
- It's really tasty. - I know.
(They eat the remaining bibimbap.)
I ate three bowls as well.
It's a bit spicy.
(They eat the remaining bibimbap.)
(Gulping down)
What's that on your neck?
A cooling patch.
- Is it a Gen Z item? - A cooling patch?
- Does it cool you down? - Yes.
- Earlier... - Do you want one?
- Yes. - Here.
- Thank you. - I'll put it on for you.
Joy brought many items.
She took care of people who were feeling hot.
- It's cool. This is incredible. - Gosh,
she is a good daughter.
Thank you.
(Grunting)
It has been a while since we came outside and ate.
- I know. - Yes.
(The 1st Rainbow Summer Retreat)
Thank you for the food. I'm so full.
- It's tasty. - We're nearly done with it.
- It's different. - We had it earlier.
- We finished it. - Yes.
Bring everything together.
I'll take it.
(They begin to clean up together.)
It's best to clean up quickly.
What should we do with the remaining food?
Pack it up for Sung Hwan.
Put it in a plastic bag.
If you press it, all of it will go in.
Let's set one aside as a prize.
(Putting the leftover in Sung Hwan's side dish container)
- It's mine, so it can't be a prize. - Let's set it aside as a prize.
- There is a lot. - I want it.
- Kian84, do you want it? - Yes, I want it.
- I'll take this. - Go ahead.
- Wasting food is bad karma. - It's bad karma.
- Let's plastic wrap it. - Of course, Kian84 wants it.
- Let's clean up. - Sung Hwan, I'll enjoy it.
Okay. Enjoy it.
- Thank you. - There is a lot.
It's a treasure.
- A treasure. - It was such a filling meal.
- We kept things clean. - Yes.
(He keeps the treasure right next to his backpack.)
All right.
We didn't come here to eat.
We need to split up into teams...
- and play games. - Teams.
Games are the highlight of the summer retreat.
There will be multiple games.
Among the similar gatherings we've hosted,
this one has the best prizes.
(Legendary prizes are ready.)
We had the best prizes...
in the ten-year history of I Live Alone.
Ten years?
I'm worried that it'll turn into a dogfight.
The prizes are incredible.
- They're almost excessive. - What?
We want a sneak peek.
Gosh, that startled me.
Will you be starring in a Peking opera today?
- The white residue will disappear. - He startled me.
Suddenly...
- He burst out laughing. - I know.
- We'll split up into three teams. - Okay.
- There will be Team Moomoo, - Okay.
Team CODE KUNST...
- Okay. - Okay.
And Team Kian84.
Three teams.
- Now, - Will we have a draw?
I'm sure you have a team you want to join.
- I want to join Team Kian84. - In that case...
(Happy)
Since everyone will want to join a certain team,
we'll have a wristband draw.
They'll be in different colors.
- Yes. - That's fair.
- Each color represents a team. - That's right.
- Okay. - That's the best way to do it.
You'll choose one at random.
The captains' colors have been decided.
Have they been decided?
We'll win if you join the team.
(Excited)
Women will get to go first.
There will be physical games as well as mental ones.
What are mental games?
(Joy goes first.)
- Pink. - It's pink.
Whose team is pink?
(Excited)
What?
(We're on the same team.)
Whose team is it?
- Hold on a second. - Is pink the only color?
(Suspicious)
They're gigglers.
How did this happen?
- This one! - Pink?
Most teams will want MINHO in that situation.
That's right.
Green.
The captains will want green.
- Green. - Let's join Team Green.
- The physical team. - Let's join the physical team.
- Please let it be green. - What?
- Ji Hyeon! - That's good.
Both of them are athletic.
- Yes, Ji Hyeon! - This is good.
- This is... - Let's go, MINHO.
Will this be okay? The members are too...
If things go like this...
Gosh, you startled me.
Toshio.
- That's a new color. - Black.
All right.
(Squeezing his eyes shut)
Bum June.
Number zero!
(All the ace members join Team Green.)
(Surprised)
All the athletic ones joined Team Green.
At this rate... Hold on.
What's this? One team will be too strong.
Black. I can feel it. It's black.
- Black. - Okay.
Team Black has a strong physique as well.
They have power.
Black!
(Sticking out his tongue)
(He is ridiculous.)
What will we do if we become the weakest team?
I know. What should we do? We'll feel bad.
- I was really worried. - We'll be bad at physical games.
- Pink. - Pink.
- Pink. - What should we do?
- They're still worried. - We're Team Weaklings.
- Green. - Nice.
Team Pink, raise your hand.
(Raising their hands)
- Team Pink. - Kim Dae Ho,
Park Gyeong Hye, and Joy.
(Team Pink)
You're Team Moomoo.
We're ruined!
Pink is Moorincess's color.
You're Team Moomoo.
We're ruined!
What should we do?
Don't even dream of winning a prize.
- There could be strategy games... - That's right.
even among physical games.
Team Green members are MINHO,
Ji Hyeon, and Bum June.
They're a physical team.
Team Kian84.
Green.
(Cheering)
- We'll win! - Yes!
(When it was MINHO's turn)
- What? - What?
- Let it be green. - Green.
- He put a magic spell on MINHO. - He whispered.
- Green. Nice. - This one!
- Green. - He hoped for it.
(I got MINHO.)
Green.
- We'll win! - Yes!
I wanted to team up with Kian84!
We have all the ace members!
- We must take first place. - This is nice.
- We must take first place. - We have the best members.
- You loved the teammates, right? - I loved the teammates.
We have the best members.
We're lovelier.
(Team Hyun Moo)
They're too strong.
We make a good team.
- We make a good team too. - I agree.
(Team CODE KUNST)
- Go! - CODE KUNST!
- CODE KUNST! - CODE KUNST!
- CODE KUNST! - Oh, my.
My teammates have the best physiques.
My team had the two musclemen.
- Exactly. - Exactly.
Here comes the bull.
(Rainbow Club's representative muscleman, Sung Hwan)
I felt reassured.
It was like having the top two ssireum champions.
(The man with the energy of the ssireum champion, Seon Min)
- CODE KUNST! - CODE KUNST!
- CODE KUNST! - No! We have the spirits!
- We won't lose. - We won't lose.
We're Team Princess.
- Hold on. Princess. - Princess.
(Cheering)
We made a good team.
- Moorincess. - Seriously.
Look at Dae Ho. He looks so out of place.
(Embarrassed)
We're ruined.
I don't have good stamina.
- You know, this is fate. - Look.
They look too gloomy.
Look. They look too gloomy.
- She is right. They look gloomy. - Look at them.
Why are you so wet?
(Grossed out)
My team is too wet.
Hey, look at him.
- What's this? - We're too wet.
- Touch me. - You aren't sweating.
- Gosh. - What?
When I put my hand on his back, it stuck due to the sweat.
Touch me.
(Hugging)
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- I'll do my best. - Kian84.
- Kian84's voice came out. - He got his spirits.
- His real voice came out. - Yes.
- "Let's go!" - "Let's go!"
Before we begin in earnest,
we prepared something to improve a sense of unity...
and teamwork.
Whenever we have a gathering, we wear matching T-shirts.
(Surprised)
- The Moo Do Ra Ji T-shirt? - No way.
- Moo Do Ra Ji? - Really?
This is like Moo Do Ra Ji, Part Two.
Moo Do Ra Ji.
(The completion certificate of the 1st Fun Run)
(Moo Do Ra Ji T-shirt)
That T-shirt was very popular.
So many people wanted it.
(I think this is really lousy!)
Did you draw again?
He is obsessed with it these days.
- Despite my busy schedule, - Moosquiat.
I drew diligently.
- Really? - Really?
It's Moosquiat's first work done on a tablet PC.
- Tablet PC? - You expanded your horizons.
- He even does digital work now. - Oh, my.
(He grew up a lot.)
(I prepared this for you guys.)
- It's pretty. - Did you really draw it?
- I drew it... - You did an amazing job.
on a tablet PC.
Of course.
Not bad.
(Rushing over)
Who is who?
- It's pretty. - It's high-quality.
It's confusing.
- My goodness. - Who is who?
I'm not in there, right?
Yes, she is.
Who is this?
(Gyeong Hye is right here.)
(200 percent in sync)
He drew a bow to let people know that it was a woman.
Otherwise, people will think that it's Seon Min.
(Wearing a princess bow)
Drawing Gyeong Hye took a long time.
- I put a lot of care into it. - You spent a lot of time on it.
Did you really put a lot of care into it?
You'll know when you see my drawing of Na Ra.
- Who is this? - Sung Hwan.
- Who? - Sung Hwan.
Come on!
What's this?
Here.
(He drew Sung Hwan with a bob.)
- CODE KUNST looks the same. - It's CODE KUNST.
He looks identical.
Who is this person with the long midface?
- Na Ra. - Na Ra.
(Is that me?)
He looks the same.
(The drawings look similar in a strange way.)
There are key characteristics.
I allocated less time to the ones I've drawn before.
(Don't misunderstand. He was pressed for time.)
- That's Dae Ho. - Is that me?
They're somewhere between mockery and realism.
Is that bread next to my face?
MINHO looks handsome.
(Props that match each member)
(Joy is pretty even in Moosquiat's work.)
- You drew Joy prettily. - Joy.
Hey, Seon Min and I...
(Seon Min...)
Hold on a second. What's that?
Hey, Seon Min and I...
(Rainbow Club members are checking out the T-shirt.)
Hold on a second. What's that?
What's that?
Why are my eyes in a different location?
What is he looking at? Does he have scleral show?
- I mean, he is always angry. - He was excited to see his.
- It's a facial composite. - Look at the details of the irises.
- I know. They're brown. - I brought out...
- the colors of his irises. - He added colors.
Which one is me?
(Moosquiat's drawing of Kian84)
- I mean... - What's that?
(It doesn't look like anyone they know.)
- Who is that? - Whom did you draw?
I drew Kian84, Na Ra, and Ji Hyeon last.
You shouldn't have drawn me.
Is there a strong fan in front of your face?
If I hadn't drawn you, you would've been disappointed.
- But... - It's too much.
- Seriously. - How is that Kian84?
(Laughing)
- Who is that? - Seon Min and I...
Who is that?
I drew myself haphazardly.
The one next to Hyun Moo annoys me the most.
(Glass noodles)
- So this is the back. - Radish.
It's so pretty.
The back was pretty.
- The front... - Radish.
- Take one each... - Okay.
and check out your face.
(The T-shirt has all the Rainbow Club members.)
What's the size? X-Large.
Did you take one out?
The shape of the eyes is identical.
Let's take a leap.
In 1, 2, 3.
- They give a sense of connection. - Exactly.
To be honest, I want three more.
- Some viewers might want it, - I know that many do.
so we're planning to release a limited edition T-shirt. Yes.
Where can it be bought?
Musinsa.
(It can be bought online as part of the proceeds are donated.)
It starts with "Mu" like "Moo, doesn't it?
It would be nice to wear with friends...
- when going on a trip. - That would be great.
Right.
If not many people buy them, I'll buy them all.
- To keep your self-esteem high? - Right. If they don't sell well,
- I'll buy them all. - Right.
Each team must come up with a team name and a chant.
- Right. - Thank you.
- Thank you - Thank you.
- You have until 3:30pm. - Okay!
(Youth Hostel)
(CODE KUNST blows the pipe.)
The piper stood out the most.
(Wriggling)
I can't help it.
I can't help but move my body.
- Gosh. - The playful young one...
and the older ones.
Sung Hwan liked doing that.
(The playful young one and the older ones)
- It's cool in here. We're in 115. - It's our room.
- It has our team name! - Gosh!
(Team Hyun Moo arrives at the lodging.)
Nice. "Team Hyun Moo."
(Team Leader Moo welcomes them at the door.)
- Gosh, it's nice! - Gosh!
Gosh, it's an old place.
That place is like...
It has that smell from the past.
- The smell from a retreat. - Right.
Rooms for several people have a certain smell.
- Right. - Right.
(Team CODE KUNST)
- Gosh! - Gosh, it's nice!
- Awesome! - But...
- Come on! - Gosh!
- Gosh, this is amazing. - It's nice.
- Gosh. - We have to decide on the beds.
It was a really nice room.
It was really nice.
We never had beds during retreats.
Right. We just had blankets.
Originally, at youth hostels,
everyone slept in a big room together.
- Over ten people in the same room. - Right.
(Around 7 to 8 people stayed in the same room.)
- There wasn't anything special, - But it was exciting.
- but we stayed up all night. - Right.
The time spent in the rooms was the best moment.
- Right. - Right.
It really feels like a retreat.
(They remember those times.)
- Even the air feels the same. - It's been so long.
- Even the air feels the same. - Right.
Gosh, this is amazing!
(They all enter their rooms.)
We have to come up with a chant.
(The members of Team Kian84 gather for the team name and chant.)
MINHO, Kian84, Ji Hyeon, and Bum June.
The MKJB Crew.
We asked ChatGPT for help.
Gosh, you guys used AI?
The Gang of Four.
Right. I got that as well.
The Four Men.
Team Intersection.
Team Intersection!
Team Intersection doesn't sound bad.
He likes that one.
- There's a chant. - The chant.
- Check it out. - Right.
Give me another suggestion if you don't like it.
"Where did we all meet up?"
And all of us say, "The intersection!"
(Bursting into laughter)
That was awful.
"How far do we go?"
"Until the end!"
And all of us say, "Let's go, Team Intersection!"
Okay.
Ji Hyeon seems to like it.
- Let's give it a try. - Right.
Where did we all meet up?
- The intersection! - The intersection!
How far do we go?
- Until the end! - Until the end!
- Let's go, Team Intersection! - Let's go, Team Intersection!
This is so lame.
- It's a bit embarrassing. - Gosh.
This is a hard thing to do.
It's really hard to come up with a team name.
For MINHO, it was his second group...
after SHINee.
- Gosh! - That's a great dishonor.
Since we're Team Intersection,
let's add meaning to our names.
- MINHO, you're Straight Ahead. - Right.
- Straight Ahead. - Straight Ahead!
You're Green Light.
- Green Light! - That suits him.
- Like TVXQ? Straight Ahead MINHO. - Right.
You do the thinking as you go straight ahead.
I see.
- You drive forward first. - Right.
- Right. - He thinks as he moves forward.
- There's a story in the name. - Right.
- We decided to add meaning. - Straight Ahead MINHO.
I'm Traffic Light.
- Traffic Light. - I see.
- That's nice. - Right.
"It's more exciting when things don't go your way."
Traffic84.
- Right. Traffic84. - Traffic84.
You're Navigation, Ji Hyeon.
- Okay. - Navigation Ji Hyeon.
You're the one who plans, mediates, and makes decisions.
- Okay. - He guides us.
- Navigation Ji Hyeon. - Navigation Ji Hyeon.
Bum June is Engine.
- Nice! - Engine!
Engine Bum June.
You have execution, responsibility, and consistency.
I like it.
- "Let's do it instead of talking." - Engine Bum June!
- "Instead of talking." - It's nice with the meaning.
- It's nice. - When MINHO goes straight ahead,
Traffic84 will find a new route.
Navigation Ji Hyeon will guide the right direction.
- Engine Bum June will push forward. - Engine Bum June will push forward.
That's nice.
- ChatGPT made all that? - There's a whole story.
A whole story was put together.
But it does sound really corny.
- But isn't being corny... - Right.
the true fun of a retreat?
- Right. Things must be childish. - Right. Team Intersection.
I love the chant.
These sessions...
- build teamwork. - Right.
I got a lot closer to the members...
- during this session. - Right.
- Team Intersection. - I'm certain...
we're much better than Team CODE KUNST.
- So that was what he said. - He put you guys down.
- That's what it means. - I can't hear anything...
from Hyun Moo's room.
(Straight Ahead MINHO checks the other rooms.)
(What about this side?)
(Team CODE KUNST's room is very loud.)
What's going on right now?
- Gosh. - CODE KUNST is strong as well.
- Are you guys arm wrestling? - Yes.
- Gosh, it's an actual retreat. - It can't be left out.
Hold on.
(I want to give it a try as well.)
My gosh.
You're so strong, Sung Hwan.
Go?
Use your strength. It's fine.
- I can win if you grab my wrist. - Let's give it a try.
- He's really strong. - Do it like this then.
He's a bit stronger than me.
(Feeling proud)
He's definitely strong.
- I'm quite strong, aren't I? - You're strong.
I got surprised by this. Out of the ones I went against,
Seon Min was one of the strongest.
But Sung Hwan...
- texted me last night. - What did he say?
Sung Hwan was so strong that he went to other schools...
to go against people in arm wrestling.
- Really? - Gosh.
I lost even when he grabbed my wrist,
but he said his ligament got pulled.
- Gosh! - Right.
- Really? - Gosh!
He hurt his legs while going against you,
- and he hurt his arms against me. - His ligament got pulled?
How pathetic.
(Full of worry)
I believe we're different from the others...
- in this way. - Right.
We have the power.
You and Seon Min have the power.
Right. We should go with a name based on that.
- I see. - Based on power?
(Thinking)
It feels like we're Between Power and Ham.
(It feels like we're Between Power and Ham.)
(That's impressive.)
Between Power and Ham.
- Ham means "older brother," - Ham?
- and he also brought ham. - It has a dual meaning.
Between Power and Ham sounds good.
Are you always full of ideas?
I just came up with something.
- This is how things are thought of. - Did this one get picked?
This is how things are thought of.
You even had a battle against others based on ideas.
- Right. - Right.
- Between Power and Ham sounds good. - Between Power and Ham?
That's a good one. Between Power and Ham.
Seon Min comes up with good ideas.
- He had a battle with ideas. - Nice.
Right.
- But this is what worries me. - What is it?
Let's say someone asks, "What's the name of your team?"
"It's Between Power and Ham!"
- "Power and Ham." - They might go, "It's what?"
"Ham!"
"Hey, Ham!"
- It's all about the confidence. - That's the chant.
- That's the chant. - That's nice.
If the name of our team is Between Power and Ham,
we can go with the chant, "Hey, Ham!"
(That's impressive.)
"Hey, Ham!" This sounds fun to say.
Let's go with that.
- I like it. - It's nice.
- "Hey, Ham!" - "Hey, Ham!"
- "Hey, Ham!" - I like ham as well.
It could go like this. "Hey, Ham!"
Why does your voice sound so strong?
- It's the confidence and energy. - Right.
- "Hey, Ham!" - "Hey, Ham!"
- This works. - We got it.
- This was why this room was noisy. - Say it after me.
- Let's go back and forth. - Let's go back and forth.
- Na Ra and I will do it together. - Right.
The bones will do it together,
and the hams will do it together.
- "Hey, Ham!" - "Hey, Ham!"
You weren't able to fit in!
Hold on!
You struggled to follow along.
At first, I sort of struggled.
But he brilliantly joins in later.
- Really? - Gosh.
- "Hey, Ham!" - "Hey, Ham!"
- Okay. - One, two, three, go!
(Blowing)
It's a cult.
(A cobra is summoned with the pipe after the chant?)
- Okay. - Let's dance when he does that!
It's like this.
- "Hey, Ham!" After that, - "Hey, Ham!"
- we start dancing. - I liked that part.
One, two, three, four!
- "Hey, Ham!" - "Hey, Ham!"
Gosh, that's going to summon a snake.
The members are getting along well.
Right.
- I really liked our team. - Same here.
No other team can beat this.
- I like this. - Right.
Gosh, that was hilarious.
That team sounds so strong. What do we do?
There's no need to feel intimidated by that.
They're going to use all of their strength.
(Rummaging)
- What's that? - You should put this up.
- What's that? - Pink carpet.
- What's that? - On your hat. It's a hair clip.
- On the brim. - I see.
Since I'm a princess?
(Ta-da!)
- It looks great on you. - It was clipped there,
- so it looked like a bald spot. - A bald spot?
It looks great on you.
- Isn't it like that? - "The Golden Bell Challenge."
- "The Golden Bell Challenge." - Right.
(Princess Dae Ho feels like someone from "The Golden Bell Challenge.")
"I'm sorry, friend!"
(A character hair clip instead of name tags)
- Doesn't it look good on him? - It does.
It's the first time in my life to wear something pink.
- Really? - Really? It suits you nicely.
It's my first time.
It looks nice with the color of your hat.
Navy and pink.
(Chuckling)
(Feeling shy)
Families with daughters feel different.
Pink!
- Pink flavor! - Pink!
Pink! Like this.
- Pink. - Pink flavor!
First place, Hye and Joy!
(Pink flavor! First place, Hye and Joy!)
"First place, Hye and Joy?"
- Gosh! - My gosh.
Doesn't it sound catchy?
It feels even more annoying because it sounds catchy.
Now, when we go home,
we'll go, "Open the door, Joy!"
- It will be stuck inside your head. - "Cook some ramyeon, Joy!"
- There you go. - It's really nice.
- This is what a catchy song is. - Gosh.
- This is what a catchy song is. - It's really nice.
- Pink! - Pink flavor!
First place, Hye and Joy!
The strawberry flavor sinks in...
- Strawberry! - after a good bite!
After a good bite!
Gosh!
(The catchy song maker comes up with his own ballad.)
It's his own ballad.
After we take turns saying pink,
we'll end with, "Pink flavor! First place, Hye and Joy!"
Right there.
Don't look down on us! Yaho!
What was that?
- "Don't look down on us!" - "Don't look down on us!"
- "Don't look down on us! Yaho!" - "Don't look down on us! Yaho!"
- Okay. - Okay. We got it.
- That's neat. - That's neat.
- All right. - Pink!
- Pink! - Pink!
- Pink flavor! - Pink flavor!
- First place, Hye and Joy! - First place, Hye and Joy!
Don't look down on us!
- Yaho! - Joy led us...
- through the whole thing. - Yaho!
I like these vibes.
That was the chant, and we'll be called Pink Velvet.
- Perfect. - Gosh.
I feel like a princess.
So we'll go with that?
So this was the energy of this room.
It feels different.
All right. Team leaders!
Gather together, team leaders.
Become cooler.
- Was everything moved like that? - Yes, it was.
There was no one else to help.
(The team leaders brought over many different things.)
Should these be placed first?
- Around the size of a judo mat? - Should we give that a try?
Like this?
We thought of games that might sound like fun.
- I see. - We picked them.
- The team leaders are different. - Young ones play this often.
Should these be filled with water, Hyun Moo?
We should fill them with water. They're too light.
- Even those were filled with water? - They did so much work.
My body is boiling up.
(This is for the retreat of the Rainbow Club members!)
(Team Hyun Moo)
All of those were stuck as well.
They did so much work.
(The preparations for the games are almost done.)
- My body feels so heavy. - It feels heavy?
- Right. - I got goosebumps.
- What are we going to do? - It feels like a sports day.
- Isn't that what I think it is? - There are obstacles.
- What is that? - Look at MINHO getting excited.
- What is that? - We don't know yet.
Oh, I know.
- I know what it is. - What is that?
- It must be Drop the Handkerchief. - What is that?
Right. Isn't it Drop the Handkerchief?
Team Chunk, come here!
Weren't you guys called Between Power and Ham?
(It's a nickname.)
Chunk One!
Chunk Two! Let's go.
(The teams gather around.)
Those must be the prizes.
- Where? - The prizes.
- Prizes? - Gifts!
- What are those? - The pink boxes!
- They're big! - I'm feeling excited.
- Shin Young! - Shin Young!
- My younger sister, Shin Young! - Gosh.
(Shin Young arrives with her bag from her radio show.)
My younger sister, Kim Shin Young!
Sung Hwan went first.
Right. Sung Hwan came first.
- You've come a long way. - Hello!
- Hello! - Hello!
- Gosh, hello! - Hi, Shin Young.
Did you come right after work?
I came right after my radio show.
- Shouldn't you put your bag inside? - Right.
She came right on time before the game started.
Gosh, you never disappoint with your loyalty.
(Shin Young's loyalty is the best.)
Shin Young should also get a shirt.
- Right. - Here's XL.
- She was given XL right away. - XL might not fit me.
- This is XL. - Right.
It's big even for us.
All of the men are wearing XL.
- We're all wearing XL. - Right.
- Hold on. - I'm going to wear XL.
Why say that all of the men are wearing XL?
It seemed like you wanted to know how big it actually was.
How big it really is. Right.
The material feels nice.
- All right, Shin Young. - Yes?
- You should pick a team as well. - Which team will she pick?
A team?
All right. One, two, three.
- Choose 1 out of 3. - I chose my team.
One, two, three!
- Gosh! - I chose my team.
- Yes! - Yes!
Everyone welcomed me.
That felt nice.
Are we here to get destroyed?
Our team is so weak!
What's wrong?
- What should Shin Young be called? - Shin Young?
We all have names.
I'm Straight Ahead MINHO.
- Right. - He's Traffic84.
- I'm Engine Bum June. - They all came up with names...
- when I wasn't there. - I'm Navigation Ji Hyeon.
- Navigation Ji Hyeon? - Right.
Pick something related to traffic.
I'll go with Speeding Shin Young.
- That's nice. - Speeding Shin Young.
Gosh, she came up with a name right away.
This is the chant for our team.
- Five-Way... - Five-Way...
- Intersection. - Intersection.
The name was changed to Five-Way Intersection right away.
- Team Five-Way Intersection. - Like this?
I'll try to follow along.
- Team Five-Way Intersection. - I'll see how things go.
- You're now in Kian84's team. - Right.
Team Moomoo, Team Kian84, and Team CODE KUNST's...
team names and chants will be revealed.
Which team will start?
- We'll go first. - Okay.
- Okay. - What's the name of your team?
The name of our team is Between Power and Ham.
- Between Power and Ham. - Between Power and Ham.
- That's nice. - Ham is a play on words.
Get ready for the chant!
- Hey, Ham! - Hey, Ham!
(Blowing)
I didn't know what that was.
I didn't understand it at all.
- That wasn't good. - We're better, right?
- Ours was put together nicely. - Right.
- That wasn't good. - That wasn't good.
- That was satisfying! - That was good!
- When guys are put together, - It's funny just for the guys.
they chuckle over things on their own.
They're the only ones that look satisfied.
- All right. Team Kian84. - Right.
- We put together a story. - We have a long story.
- We'll start with the story. - A story?
(Let's hear it.)
- All of us... - Right.
were lost.
These five souls didn't know where to go...
in this crazy world.
Then, we met each other at the Five-Way Intersection.
(We met each other at the Five-Way Intersection.)
They switched it to Five-Way Intersection!
In this crazy and complicated world,
we got together at the Five-Way Intersection.
We would've reached a short distance on our own.
Now, the five of us...
- can go even further together. - It's so long!
Yes!
It's a toast!
It's the principal's speech!
It sounded like my wedding officiant's address.
(It sounded like my wedding officiant's address.)
- It sounds just the same. - We're Team Five-Way Intersection!
- "Five-Way Intersection!" - The members...
will now be introduced!
(Feeling bored)
- Gosh, it's boring. - It's so long!
- It's so exciting! - It's so exciting!
You can never arrive without departing.
- Gosh! - I will continue to move across...
- the paths avoided by others. - That's awful.
I'm Team Five-Way Intersection's Straight Ahead MINHO!
- Nice one! That was nice and bold. - Gosh!
- Straight Ahead MINHO. - Are you lost?
I will be your guide.
I'm Navigation Ji Hyeon.
(Team Five-Way Intersection's Navigation Ji Hyeon)
Are you exhausted?
I'm starting to feel exhausted.
I'm the heart of Team Five-Way Intersection.
- The heart. - I'm the youngest member...
who always encourages others.
I'm Engine Bum June.
- Yes! - Nice one!
He called himself Engine.
- Engine? - He used to be a normal guy.
Speeding isn't allowed while driving,
but I will speed toward your hearts!
I'm Speeding Shin Young!
(Team Five-Way Intersection's Speeding Shin Young)
- She did that as soon as she came. - Shin Young...
wasn't in the room, right?
- I wasn't there. - She was the best out of them.
Stop at the red light!
Think at the yellow light!
Pace forward at the green light!
- When will it end? - Pace forward at the green light!
- Go! - I'm Traffic84!
- Yes! - When will it end?
Where did we meet?
- Five-Way Intersection! - Five-Way Intersection!
- I'm slightly off. - Five-Way Intersection!
How far will we go?
- Until the end! - Until the end!
One, two!
- Let's go, - Let's go,
- Team Five-Way Intersection! - Team Five-Way Intersection!
- Until the end! - Gosh, the whole thing was done.
- I think we were better. - Right.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Let's go!
Five, six, seven, eight.
(We can't lose to them.)
- Hey, Ham! - Hey, Ham!
One, two!
- Let's go, - Let's go,
- Team Five-Way Intersection! - Team Five-Way Intersection!
We haven't gone yet!
- Right. - Right.
- Attention! - Attention!
Two, three.
- Happiness! - Happiness!
- Hello, this is Pink Velvet! - Hello, this is Pink Velvet!
- Pink! - Pink!
- Pink flavor! - Pink flavor!
First place, Hye and Joy!
(I can't watch this.)
I got goosebumps.
Look at his face!
(Look at his face!)
CODE KUNST looked disgusted.
Don't look down on us!
- Yaho! - Yaho!
- Gosh! - They copied everything.
Those legs!
What's wrong with them?
- I hated those legs the most! - Hold on.
Dae Ho did much better than I thought.
Dae Ho did well.
(In between the princesses,)
(Dae Ho couldn't fit in.)
- Look at Dae Ho's legs! - Dae Ho did well.
(He finally becomes a princess.)
I still get reminded of that.
- Why are you acting cute? - This is our team!
(Dae Ho is perfectly settled.)
The highlight of that move is the legs.
- The Yaho move. - Right.
- The gyaru move. - I hated how his legs...
went up and down like a spring after he struck the pose.
- That was perfect. - That was perfect.
- Ours was perfectly put together. - We took the stage.
- What's this? - Gosh.
Wasn't this from someone else?
- We were better. - We were better.
- Right. - We were better.
We had a better level of completion.
- We had a story. - Right.
- A story... - Right.
full of touching vibes.
- We're on top by a big difference. - Right.
According to Kian84,
the first game is something played often by young people.
- What could it be? - The Parachute Race!
- Parachute Race? - What's the Parachute Race?
The parachute is worn.
You have to run against the wind resistance.
You see the turning points, right?
Each runner must go around the turning point and come back.
It's a relay race.
The first team to come back becomes the winner.
But there are 4 members for these 2 teams.
Our team has five people.
- Another one of us will run again. - Okay.
For the order, I should run first if I'm going to...
- run one more time. - Right.
I have to save up my energy.
Man, woman, man, woman?
Running well is one thing,
but I think it'll be important...
- to take it off quickly. - Okay.
If Na Ra goes 4th and 5th,
we don't have to pass the parachute.
He can just run with it.
- You're right. - Right?
Let's start then. Who is going to run for this team?
- Hey, Ham! - Hey, Ham!
- Hey, Ham! - Why are we so off sync?
What's with the pipe sound?
- Pink Velvet. Yaho! - Yaho!
All right. One, two!
- Team Five-Way Intersection! - Team Five-Way Intersection!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
MINHO, signal us the start.
- MINHO, you do it. - Okay.
(The referee for the Parachute Race sets off.)
The Pepper Family is going first.
- We were the Pepper Family. - Right, they're all pepper lovers.
Hyun Moo, Shin Young,
- and Sung Hwan. - That's right.
- Shin Young, don't get hurt. - I won't get hurt.
- MINHO kept worrying about us. - Everyone, don't get hurt!
(Everyone, don't get hurt.)
Let's go!
- Beardping, yaho! - Yaho!
- Beardping? - I was Beardping.
- I'll speed for the prize! - That's great!
- Speeding Shin Young, let's go! - Speeding Shin Young, let's go!
All right. You can start when I give you the signal.
- Lift it up. - Okay. I'll lift it up.
It's nerve-racking.
(Nervous)
Get ready!
- Go! - Let's go!
- Hey! - Hurry!
- Gosh, Shin Young... - She's so fast.
- She's so fast. - She has the proper form.
- Go! - Let's go!
- Run! - You got this!
- Gosh, Shin Young... - She's so fast.
- She's so fast. - She has the proper form.
- Gosh! - Shin Young is fast.
- She's fast. - She's good.
What is this?
(Shin Young takes the lead from the start unexpectedly.)
- Beardping! - He's staggering.
The parachute created a lot of air resistance.
- Hurry up. - Shin Young is fast.
She's really fast. They're at the same pace.
Gosh, Brother Shin Young.
Brother? Hold on.
Come on. That was bad.
(Speeding Brother Shin Young)
She makes a good turn too.
- It's a reset for us. - She's in first place.
(She even turned the tables.)
- Gosh. - She's fast.
- Come in! - She's too fast.
Here. Run!
All right.
All right. Let's go!
- He's running at full speed. - What?
Let's go.
Ji Hyeon.
He was fast.
All right. Let's go!
- Gosh, it's a monkey. - Mr. Saru.
- The monkey expression... - Mr. Saru!
wasn't on point.
- It's Mr. Saru. - Mr. Saru.
Mr. Saru.
- Mr. Saru! - He's really fast.
- Go! - Nice!
Run!
Gosh, what is this?
(Flailing due to the parachute's air resistance)
The air resistance was stronger than expected.
Oh, no.
(Feeling bad for her)
- Fruitping! - Fruitping!
- "Fruitping?" - We all had our own characters.
- What kind of ping were you? - Eyeballping.
Eyeballping?
- Ji Hyeon! - Go!
Nice!
- He ran well. - He did well.
- CODE KUNST! - Go!
(CODE KUNST, Ji Hyeon)
Wait a minute.
(Pink Velvet is over a half lap behind.)
(Screaming)
- Fruitping! - Fruitping!
Fruitping!
- It's okay. You finished it. - It's okay.
Here. Put it on.
- Put it on. - They're just having fun with it.
- You go. - Run!
That's it.
Let's go! Run!
Let's go!
Bum June...
(Screaming)
Bum June runs well.
He's really fast.
(Screaming)
Here we go!
Eyeballping is off.
I did my best.
(Skipping)
- It was fun. - Eyeballping.
Nice. You got it. You can go.
(In the fierce relay race...)
- She's jogging? - Oh, no.
(Jogging relaxedly)
You're doing well.
- You're doing well. - You did it.
- You did it. - Run!
(What's more important than the race is the princesses' dignity.)
- "The princesses' dignity?" - "The princesses' dignity?"
- It's okay. - Let's go!
What's important is finishing the race.
(Meanwhile, Between Power and Ham and Team Five-Way Intersection...)
(are neck and neck.)
Go!
- Here. - Hold it for him.
- Go! - Kian84!
The team leader!
Kian84!
- Goodness. - Hey!
I couldn't put it on.
I know. It's harder than it looks.
- You're rushed too. - I couldn't put it on.
(Surprised)
Hey!
- He took off his cap right away. - He's so cool.
With Fun Run's pride on the line.
Proper Runner versus Fun Runner!
Fun Runner wins.
Go!
- Okay, Na Ra! - Na Ra!
(Na Ra turns the tables.)
- He turned the tables. - He turned the tables?
Na Ra runs fast in short-distance races.
Next! Who's next?
- It's not me. - Na Ra, go one more time.
He has to go one more time.
(The last runner, Na Ra)
The fifth runners are the aces of their teams.
- That's right. - We have MINHO. We'll win.
- Since we have MINHO... - It's MINHO!
- It's not me. - Go one more time.
He has to go one more time.
Let's go!
- Right away? - What? He's running one more time?
It's MINHO!
(Ace MINHO sets off.)
- All right. - Go, MINHO!
Go now!
We must win!
- What was that? - So that's how he ran.
He's no joke.
- Are you sure he put it on? - What's with him?
(Chasing furiously against the air resistance)
Gosh, it's MINHO.
Gosh, MINHO is fast.
You're almost there!
Na Ra!
He's so fast.
Na Ra lost all his energy.
He did two laps by himself.
He runs so well. Goodness.
Na Ra, hang in there!
You can do it!
Goodness. But...
MINHO!
Look. MINHO is no joke.
- He ran so well. - Na Ra is tired.
First place!
We won first place!
(Team Five-Way Intersection won.)
We did it.
You got this.
Gosh, that was amazing.
Well done.
(He lost by a hair.)
(Disappointed)
- We're in second place, right? - Yes, we are.
Well done.
- After a lap, - It's really tiring.
I was almost out of energy.
- Right. - Of course it's tiring.
- It's tiring. - You ran two laps.
- Your leg gave way, right? - When Na Ra came in...
after two laps,
he aged in that short amount of time.
- All of a sudden. - That's right.
- His dark circles were darker. - They were.
He got more under-eye fat.
(Joking)
- Goodness. - It was all sunken like sink holes.
- You should reposition it. - Goodness.
Well done.
(Still, you did well.)
- Where are we? - Our ace just set off.
- Oh, really? Who is it? - Yes.
Hey!
(The last princess, Moorincess, sets off.)
You got to walk...
- the red carpet by yourself. - Of course.
A solo shot.
- He's coming in by himself. - Princesses love solo shots.
(Everyone's attention is on Moorincess.)
- Yaho! - Yaho!
Princesses' stroll?
- Our princess. - A stroll.
Well done.
He had a Fun Run.
I had a Fun Run there too.
Their team...
- Yes! - Good job.
At the end, when you were neck and neck...
MINHO ran like an engine.
- He wins every time he plays. - He beat the wind.
Gosh, we should've taken turns. It was a fail.
(Making Na Ra go 4th and 5th was a failed strategy.)
Running two laps in a row must've been really tiring.
(Groaning)
- Oh, no, Sung Hwan. - It was really hard on Sung Hwan,
- and I was also... - Oh, no...
- It was really hard. - We thought of the parachute...
too easily.
- That's right. - I thought it'd be nothing.
Gosh, a comeback win.
- Who is that? - I didn't think it was you.
It's the person from the drawing.
(The person from the drawing)
That's not true.
- I drew that. - They look the same.
By the way, Shin Young was really fast.
I was really surprised.
You came in first.
- She did track and field. - She was a track and field athlete.
- She was a track and field athlete. - When I was in seventh grade.
You were really fast.
I did track and field in seventh grade.
Then I switched to judo.
- It wasn't just judo. - That's how it was.
Everyone knew MINHO would run well.
- He's really fast. - But...
it never occurred to us that Shin Young would be fast.
- That's right. - Everyone thought I was expendable.
- We thought she'd be caught up. - I thought so too.
If Shin Young didn't run like this, your team would've won.
- That's right. - That's right.
Hold on.
What is it?
- One of us... - Yes?
- ran... - Yes.
without the parachute on for a certain distance.
- What? - Who is it?
- Who is it? - There's a VAR in pro sports games.
Who is it?
- VAR. - Who is it?
- Hold on. - Isn't it Kian84?
- No. - Come on.
- He did wear it. - Wait.
- He ran without it. - No.
He was wearing it.
- Oh, for this section. - Look at that.
- He ran without wearing it. - He ran too far.
- That's not it. Look. - He ran...
around 1.5m without wearing it.
That's why we stopped.
- We were supposed to... - Wait.
- wear it properly. - That's right.
- For sure. - Then we could run.
He ran while carrying it.
- Who is it? - No, he put his arms through it.
- No way. - Disqualified!
- Come on. - Come on.
- Let's go. - Come on.
- Come on. - Seriously.
It's a red card.
(Bitter)
How about one more round for a rematch?
- No. We can't. - Darn it.
Stop it already.
It's Lee Gye In.
Father.
A few of us are down, feeling ill.
No, I won't run.
All right. Let's have a rematch.
- I'm sorry. - A rematch.
- Sorry about that. - You said okay without hesitation.
- I was cool about it. - You were cool about it.
- Let's have a rematch. - A rematch!
- Are you okay with a rematch? - Yes.
- Gosh. - Should I run two laps in a row?
No. Then...
- You should go second. - Second.
- Second. - I'll go third.
- Four, five. - You'll go second and fifth.
- After a game... - We realized it.
CODE KUNST is our master strategist.
Yes, you need to use your brain.
We pass the parachute like this.
When I take it off,
- you shouldn't go like this. - Go the other way around.
- Like this. - It takes longer if you fasten it.
Right. Don't fasten it. Put it on like this.
Teamwork is really important...
because it takes a long time to put the parachute on.
- That's right. - Seriously.
- Okay. - What do we do?
We just need to do our best.
- Yes, we will. - We just need to do our best.
I thought I was fast when I was running earlier.
- Yes, you ran well. - You did well.
- We're slow at turning, so... - That's right.
- Team Princesses... - You did well.
- is supporting each other well. - Well done.
- Among the princesses. - You did well.
- I'll run as fast as possible. - This time,
why don't you run twice, Dae Ho?
- Will you go, Dae Ho? - You should run twice.
- You run well, though. - A long stroll makes you sweat.
- You're pushing it to each other. - Because it was tiring.
- Still, Dae Ho must run better. - Of course.
- Okay. - He's been working out constantly.
- We got this! - Gyeong Hye.
- Yes? Let's stand well. - All right.
- Let's go! - Pink Velvet!
Shall we do a chant before we start?
- Let's go. - Let's go!
- Pink. - Pink.
- Pink Velvet. Yaho. - Pink.
- Yaho. - It's a mess.
- Team Five-Way Intersection! - Team Five-Way Intersection!
- Let's go! That's enough. - Go!
- Everyone was exhausted. - I was exhausted.
- Hey, Ham! - Hey, Ham!
Let's do this!
Actually, I was a little lazy to play the pipe from then.
I knew it. The pipe was gone at some point.
Sung Hwan isn't well.
Let's start!
- Let's go, Speeding Shin Young! - Let's go!
You can do it if you think you can do it!
- You can't. - It'll be good if you say so.
Get ready!
(Parachut Race, rematch)
- Go! - Yes!
- Let's go! - You can do it!
- Gosh, Shin Young. - Look at her.
- Goodness. - She doesn't even stagger.
Shin Young, we're in first place!
- She's really fast. - Look at Sung Hwan.
She's the fastest among them.
(Shin Young is leading this time as well.)
- Look at her form. - You can do it!
- She's dying. - Gyeong Hye...
- That's great! - She's so fast.
- Goodness! You unfastened it. - Did you see that?
- Shin Young is really good. - Gosh, Shin Young...
- Well done! - Go!
- You did really well. - Go!
- Well done. - Go!
(Team CODE KUNST's Na Ra versus Team Kian84's Ji Hyeon)
- I'll do it. - Go, Ji Hyeon!
- Na Ra is fast. - Yes, he's fast.
- Na Ra is fast. - Na Ra is fast.
- Na Ra is fast. - Ji Hyeon is fast too.
- Ji Hyeon is fast. - Ji Hyeon is fast.
(Na Ra is just as fast as nimble Ji Hyeon.)
- He's strong. - Let's go, Ji Hyeon!
Let's go!
(Save the princess!)
It looks like he's injured already.
- It's so tiring. - He's here!
(The balance is still kept well.)
- Let's go! - That's great.
- Let's go, Bum June! Just run! - Go!
- CODE KUNST is fast. - He's fast.
Mr. Saru.
- Mr. Saru! - Mr. Saru.
Because you're trying to keep a poker face,
- you can't pick up speed. - I know.
I'd have been faster if I frowned more.
- You didn't frown as much. - Mr. Saru.
(Mr. Saru, stop right there!)
Run!
- Run! - I should put it on fast.
All right. It's Kian84.
(It's my turn now.)
Run!
(He took the parachute with nervous tension.)
- Put it on and run! - No!
- Put it on! - Put it on first!
- Put it on! - You're cheating again!
- Put it on first. - Oh, no.
Come on!
Look at that.
You're used to cheating.
He didn't want to be a burden to the team.
- I know. - I felt rushed.
He had to do it even though he felt rushed.
(He fell behind while putting on the parachute.)
(This is our chance!)
(Screaming)
Well done. Are you coming back from school?
You were relaxed, Beardping.
I have to run.
(He's relaxed in any kind of situation.)
(The dignity of a princess)
Kian84!
(The gap has widened quite a bit.)
- Take it. - Let's go!
Great. Go!
(Team CODE KUNST's last runner, Na Ra)
- He set off by himself. - Gosh, Na Ra...
(He set off by himself, outpacing his competitors.)
MINHO. Yes, go. Go after putting it on!
(Team Kian84's last runner, MINHO)
- Look at MINHO. - Look at his eyes.
The last one.
You're almost there, Na Ra!
- MINHO! - Let's go!
(We believe in you, MINHO.)
- Na Ra! - MINHO!
Gosh, Hyun Moo.
(An unexpected appearance of Princess Moomoo)
- That's seriously... Beardping! - It was a fair tackle.
- It was a fair tackle. - You got in MINHO's way.
That's cheating.
- It was the wind. - That's what you call cheating.
- He got in the way! - Sir!
- No! - He got in the way!
(Screaming)
- No! - What?
(Flapping)
Why did you drag that along?
What a fool.
- A handicap. - Seriously...
He made it even harder for himself.
Disqualified.
(A handicap no one gave)
(He gave it to himself and sprinted furiously.)
(Glancing over)
No!
(Princess Moomoo's fair interruption)
Princess Moomoo.
- This is our chance! - Gosh.
MINHO!
We won!
(Na Ra passed the finish line first.)
Gosh, we won.
(He beat the strongest MINHO and won hands down.)
He had two crises.
He was carrying the cone, and the princess interrupted him.
- That's right. - The two crises...
- He overcame that. - He overcame that.
That's the princess's wit.
You didn't know you were carrying the cone?
I didn't. I didn't know at first.
You run really fast. You won first place even with that.
It's almost like off-season training.
- I had no idea. - With that,
you must've thought the wind suddenly picked up.
- I know. - Yes. I thought....
it was a strong air resistance.
"Why the sudden gust?"
Na Ra will be good at short-distance runs.
If he runs 100m.
- For how long did he carry this? - He carried this too.
For how long did you carry this?
Na Ra was in a different event by himself.
- A Marine Corps boot camp. - It was probably like a 10km run.
Sung Hwan is napping, basically.
- Sung Hwan! - He's gone.
- Sung Hwan. - Sung Hwan passed out.
- Sung Hwan. - Sung Hwan is in Phuket by himself.
- I ran while carrying it? - You ran while carrying again.
- No, I... - You did. Disqualified.
Hyun Moo! I have a question.
- Why did you run only four times? - What do you mean?
I have a question. Why did you run only four times?
- What? - You only ran four times.
- I carried this too. - They didn't run five times?
- I carried this. - What?
- They should've run one more time. - They ran only four times.
They ran only four times.
They should've run one more time.
- We all ran 5 times. - Oh, they ran only 4 times?
- He's running. - He's going now.
They should've run one more time.
(Princess Dae Ho rushes out.)
- He's going now. - Dae Ho!
We're not done yet.
We're not done yet, so why...
- He might pull that at the end. - We're still in the race.
- This is how you run properly. - Be careful!
- Go ahead. - We're still in the race.
Let's go, Dae Ho.
- We finished the race. - We finished the race.
How did you win first place with this thing hanging?
- We all got the hang of it. - We did really well.
We did well. Gosh, I'm so dizzy.
- Here comes the prize. - Let's go get the prize.
- Here comes the prize. - Oh, the prize.
I'll bring it over.
- What is it? - It looks heavy.
Between Power and Ham, focus.
- It looked heavy. - I got excited.
- Right. - Seriously.
One, two...
We give you a premium aged Korean beef gift set!
(It's none other than a premium aged Korean beef gift set.)
It was worth running four laps.
- Yes, you deserved it. - It was worth running four laps.
- He deserved it. - We should've given all to him.
I felt really proud of it.
The cut looks delicious.
It's not just one pack per person.
It's a box per person.
(It's a box per person.)
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Gosh, how did you run while carrying that?
I know. He's smazing.
- Gosh. - Gosh, it's hot.
(After the Parachute Race...)
I'm dying.
- Gosh, it was really hard then. - That's right.
- It's because it was hot. - You're right.
(Having a refreshing drink to beat the heat)
Are you perfectly fine?
Of course.
You don't feel tired at all?
- No. - Is he a pro soccer player or what?
(Recovering thanks to the younger one's massage)
- About 15 seconds? - Gosh, you're really fast.
Her record was 15 seconds for 100m.
Why were you sulking there?
- Because he was disqualified. - Well, I...
I didn't like the rules too. We were supposed to be winners.
- The artist. - He was upset.
(Glancing over)
- You're okay, right? - Yes.
- You looked upset. - What?
You look upset.
Kian84, it's okay. It's okay to lose.
- We did better. - Of course we did.
Yes, we did better.
He takes good care of older guys.
- It's okay. - Gosh, MINHO...
has people wrapped around his finger.
Have people wrapped around his finger?
(Meanwhile, the other older guys...)
(Grunting)
Gosh, I'm dying here.
Goodness.
(Exhausted)
(They dropped one by one in the end.)
You really can't hide your age.
Of course not.
Those over 40 all took a nap like that.
- My dad looks like that. - You look the same.
I'm not in my 40s yet.
You're right.
(While those in their 40s dropped dead...)
(Screaming)
Oh, this one?
Oh, goodness.
- A youth drama. "Our Paradise." - You're right.
(A scene from a youth drama)
One, two!
Let's play the next game.
(They play the next game.)
If the camera captures you, then you're dead.
You die if you get captured.
This is fun!
(The one who's trying to take a photo)
(And the ones who are trying to avoid)
Look at him.
I think I was captured too much.
- Gosh, I'm tired. - Teamwork was really important.
Seriously...
- Go, Team Five-Way Intersection! - Blind...
- Let's go! - Water Carrying Game!
- Let's go! - Go!
- Let's go! - That's crazy!
They're on a roll!
Oh, no!
(Refreshing)
Shin Young!
What was that?
Shin Young, scoop a lot.
Slow down, Shin Young!
Goodness.
I didn't know that happened.
They fell down and everything. It was crazy.
Hey! Pass it properly!
You should go too.
Aim properly before passing!
(The Rainbow Retreat is in full swing.)
Which way should we go?
Come this way.
Let's go.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Goodness. Great job!
The feeling after the retreat ends...
- I know. - You know...
the steamed egg that's like pudding?
Come this way.
(Come this way.)
- Gosh. - We're here.
We haven't had a meal in a cafeteria for so long.
It was really cool as soon as we entered.
That's right.
Gosh, that vibe.
- This kind of vibe. - We haven't seen that in a while.
- Let's sit down. - Sit here.
Sit here in a row.
- Okay. - Let's go!
- Follow me. - Let's sit.
Sit down.
- All right. - Follow me.
- Everyone can sit at this table. - Yes, everyone can sit here.
Like a school.
Now, go back to your rooms and wash.
- Sounds good. - And take your time...
to prepare for the talent show.
- Okay. - Okay.
All right.
President Jun, is there a prize for the talent show?
Of course.
Actually, the real prizes...
are all for the talent show.
He said there's an electronic device for the prize.
Yes, there is.
- You gave up? - It's more than 500 or 600 dollars.
- It's the winning prize. - For real?
That's why the talent show is important.
- Isn't it an electric car? - Yes, it is.
(Isn't it an electric car?)
That's right.
- I can't wait. - I can't wait also.
Shall we get going?
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Let's meet after washing.
(Next story)
(The long-awaited talent show finally starts.)
(What are you doing?)
(Oh, we can't show them.)
(Suspicion and vigilance toward each other)
(Their moves become more desperate.)
(As they're anxious, they recall the petty tricks from school days.)
(A discreet casting operation in progress)
(You'll give me shares?)
(20 percent)
(Deal)
(The participants gather after a thorough preparation.)
(Prizes on a surprising scale)
(Surprised)
(Working in uniti is over. It's war now.)
(The one going after me better brace themselves.)
(I'm going to win 1st place, no matter what.)
(A series of performances that catch them off guard)
(I'm going to...)
(give it my all today.)
(Beyond anything you can imagine)
She's covering her eyes again.
(A fiery war of nerves)
(What's the point of saying that now, you punk?)
(It's getting increasingly heated.)
(Eventually, some people drop out.)
This is not cool.
(The Cruel Chronicles of Talent Show)
(A legendary idol...)
(who needs no introduction)
(The main dancer of...)
(the nation's favorite girl group, Girls' Generation)
(A singer and an actress)
(Yu Ri)
(Taking a sip of tea elegantly in the morning)
(A view of Seongsan Ilchulbong)
(This is why I live on Jeju Island.)
(Her first time living alone on Jeju Island)
(It's been 3 years since I started living in Jeju alone.)
(Filled with items that give off the Jeju vibe)
(Life in Jeju is full of romance.)
(Life in Jeju is very humid.)
(Frames warped by humidity...)
(and a wall covered in mold)
(The morning on an island is war against humidity.)
(Using all sorts of items to control humidity)
(What? Is it a bug?)
(Screaming)
(Then she has a war against bugs.)
(Shall I go find something to eat?)
(I'll pick only as much as I'll eat.)
(Free grocery shopping at the Jeju sea)
(Fresh seasonal hijiki is everywhere.)
(Multi-Talented Yu Ri's Island)